The first year of school can be stressful – not for the kids, but for the parents!
上学的第一年可能会让人感到压力——不是对孩子，而是对父母！
They want their little ones to do well at school and some pushy parents will already be thinking about how they can get their child to the top of the class.
他们希望自己的孩子在学校表现良好，一些执意强求的父母已经在考虑如何让孩子成为班级中的佼佼者。
But some parents are concerned about the rules for when children should start school.
但一些家长对儿童何时应该上学的规则感到担忧。
The School Admissions Code for England says that children must join the reception class the September after their fourth birthday.
英格兰的《学校招生法》规定，孩子们必须在四岁生日后的九月加入学前班。
But here is the problem: A four year old who is born in August could be in the same class as someone who was born in October of the previous year!
但问题是：一个八月出生的四岁孩子可能与上一年十月出生的孩子在同一班级！
Both of them were four years old in September.
他们在九月时都是四岁。
The older child will probably do better in class tests.
年龄较大的孩子可能会在班级测试中表现得更好。
He or she is almost a year older!
他或她几乎比其他小朋友年长一岁！
This can affect the confidence of the younger child.
这可能会影响年幼孩子的自信心。
Now England's schools minister, Nick Gibbs says that the rules should be changed.
现在，英格兰的学校部长尼克·吉布斯（Nick Gibbs）表示，应该改变这些规则。
In an open letter to councils, schools and parents he says, "Parents know their children best".
他在给议会、学校和家长的公开信中说：“父母最了解他们的孩子。”
And he said that some parents "feel forced to send their child to school before they are ready".
他还说，一些家长“感到被迫在孩子还没准备好之前就送他们上学”。
He proposes that children that are born during the summer can join the class when they are four or wait until they are five.
他提议，夏季出生的孩子可以在四岁时加入班级，或者等到五岁。
Dr. David Whitebread, an educationalist from Cambridge University says that the UK has a summer-born effect because children start school so young.
剑桥大学的教育学家大卫·怀特布雷德（David Whitebread）博士表示，英国存在“夏季出生效应”，因为孩子们开始上学的年龄太小。
"In countries with these later starting ages, there is a very much reduced summer-born effect or none at all", he said.
他说：“在入学年龄较晚的国家，夏季出生效应大大减少，甚至完全不存在。”